

Software Developer

Jorge R. Sarabia

Argentina

+595981405675

http://sarabiajor.ge

ă

https://github.com/jorgesarabia

m

linkedin.com/in/jorgesarabia/

@

jorge@sarabiajor.ge

Skills -

Spanish(Native)

Ionic 3

Flutter

JavaScript

Javascrip

PHP

Git

Angular

Firebase

English

Flask

(*)Scale from 0 (Beginner) to 6 (Expert)

Personal Aims

In pursuit of continuous learning supported by work stability and responsibility, I would like to continue improving my skills as a mobile developer. I have been developing hybrid software with Ionic for more than 3 years and I am currently developing applications with Flutter. I also have some experience working with Java and Kotlin.

Experience

Since 2018 Software Developer at Noted Analytics, Inc.

Boston MA, USA

It is a company that develops a web application for salesforce. From October 2018 to October 2019 my task was unit testing the frontend of the system, which is developed with Angular 6, unsing the Jasmine framework. Since October 2019 I have been developing the mobile application with Flutter.

https://www.notedanalytics.com/

2018-2019 Software Developer at Autotall.

Córdoba, ARG

It is a company that provides a SaaS focused on the sales of vehicles. From October 2018 to October 2019 I was in charge of the mobile application with Ionic 3, launching it for both Android and iOS.

https://autotall.com.ar/

Since 2016 Freelance Software Developer.

Online

I develop web pages and mobile applications, using technologies such as Ionic 3, Java, Kotlin, Flutter, Bulma and Bootstrap. Also Backend with Firebase, Laravel and a little experience with Flask, Django and I am currently learning Ruby on Rails.

Education

Since 2019 Student at Platzi.

Online

It is a platform where people can study several technologies. There I study and specialize in everything related to my career, I have several courses completed there. You can check my profile at.

https://platzi.com/@jorgesarabia/

Since 2018 English Course.

Online

I have been studying with a private teacher since October 2018. We have online classes through Skype and Zoom two times a week.

2016

Electronic Engineer. Universidad Católica Nuestra Señora de la Asunción, PAR I have been an electronic engineer since 2016, during my university studies we focused on both software and hardware. My undergraduate thesis was based on a People Counter through images from video

cameras, which I developed with C++ and OpenCV libraries.

[Further Information]

I am keen on Debian Operating System. Lately I have been actively developing several open-source projects. I enjoy learning new technologies and improving my programming skills every day, which is why I consider myself an eternal student.